Guide to the Toba Pato Tucker Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, circa 1970-2003; Series I; (190 boxes)
  - Exhibition Prints, (73 boxes)
    - 11 inches by 14 inches
      - Heber Spring Portraits
        - Cindy McCord, 1990 May 9 (Box 19, Folder 517)
        - Cindy McCord and Gail McCord, 1990 May 9 (Box 19, Folder 518)
        - Gail McCord, 1990 May 9 (Box 19, Folder 519)
        - Tanya Sheley, 1990 May 9 (Box 19, Folder 520-522)
        - Todd Spinks, 1990 May 10 (Box 19, Folder 523)
        - Irma Dean Verser, 1990 May 12 (Box 19, Folder 524)
        - J. C. Verser, 1990 May 12 (Box 19, Folder 525)
        - Benjamin Johnston, 1990 May 13 (Box 19, Folder 526)
        - Estelle "Sissy" Hazelwood, 1990 May 14 (Box 19, Folder 527-528)
        - Margaret Bittle, 1990 May 19 (Box 19, Folder 529)
        - Tatum Bittle, 1990 May 19 (Box 19, Folder 530)
        - Elizabeth Davis, Tammara Davis, and Tiffany Cooper, 1990 June 1 (Box 20, Folder 531-532)
        - Elizabeth Davis and Tammara Davis, 1990 June 1 (Box 20, Folder 533)
        - Janice Hipp Verser, 1990 June 1 (Box 20, Folder 534)
        - Julia Chamness Carr, 1990 June 2 (Box 20, Folder 535)
        - Tricia Carr Spinks, 1990 June 2 (Box 20, Folder 536)
        - Louisa Cooke, 1990 June 7 (Box 20, Folder 537)
        - Henry McMahan, 1990 June 7 (Box 20, Folder 538)
        - Ida Bullard Stark, 1990 June 21 (Box 20, Folder 539)
        - Thomas Ivy "Pete" Stark, 1990 June 21 (Box 20, Folder 540)
        - Mary Bittle Thurman, 1990 July 15 (Box 20, Folder 541)
        - Randy Thurman, 1990 July 15 (Box 20, Folder 542)
        - Budd Higgs, 1990 October 10 (Box 20, Folder 543)
        - Nancy Bullard Donaldson, 1990 October 20 (Box 20, Folder 544)
        - Rachel Klarer and Sandra Cox, 1990 October 20 (Box 20, Folder 545)
        - Mekay Partridge, 1990 October 21 (Box 20, Folder 546)
        - Sylvia Roy, 1990 October 20 (Box 20, Folder 547)
        - Geneva Jauch, 1990 October 23 (Box 20, Folder 548)
        - Harry Neukam, 1990 October 24 (Box 20, Folder 549)
        - Dudley Lemon, 1990 November 2 (Box 21, Folder 550)
        - Sam Haile and Steve Haile, 1990 November 8 (Box 21, Folder 551)
        - James Dayze, 1990 November 11 (Box 21, Folder 552)
        - Nancy Dayze and Wayne Dayze, II, 1990 November 11 (Box 21, Folder 553)
        - David Dick, 1990 November 11 (Box 21, Folder 554)
        - Bynam Bullard, 1990 November 13 (Box 21, Folder 555)
        - Fred Byford, 1990 November 14 (Box 21, Folder 556)
        - Clayce Cannon and Dorothy Peel Cannon, 1990 November 14 (Box 21, Folder 557)
        - Dorothy Peel Cannon, 1990 November 14 (Box 21, Folder 558)
        - Rex Harrall, 1990 November 15 (Box 21, Folder 559)
        - Victor Lee Presley, 1990 November 17 (Box 21, Folder 560)
        - Allison Patchell, 1990 November 18 (Box 21, Folder 561)
        - Douglas Patchell and Allison Patchell, 1990 November 18 (Box 21, Folder 562)
        - A. M. "Andy" Killion, 1990 November 19 (Box 21, Folder 563-564)
        - A. M. "Andy" Killion, E. W. "Elmer" Killion, and C. M. "Clifford" Killion, 1990 November 19 (Box 21, Folder 565-566)
        - C. M. "Clifford" Killion, 1990 November 19 (Box 21, Folder 567)
        - E. W. "Elmer" Killion, 1990 November 19 (Box 21, Folder 568)
        - B. L. "Bozy" Johnston and Bill Johnston, 1990 November 25 (Box 21, Folder 569)
        - B. L. "Bozy" Johnston, Bill Johnston, Benjamin Johnston, and Matthew Johnston, 1990 November 25 (Box 21, Folder 570)
        - Benjamin Johnston and Matthew Johnston, 1990 November 25 (Box 21, Folder 571)
        - Joe Fricker and Ray Fricker, 1990 November 28 (Box 21, Folder 572)
        - Louise Fricker, 1990 November 28 (Box 21, Folder 573)
        - Ray Fricker, 1990 November 28 (Box 21, Folder 574)
        - Carlos Killion, 1991 January 9 (Box 22, Folder 575)
        - William J. Allbright, 1991 January 17 (Box 22, Folder 576)
        - J. A. "Jerry" Moon, 1991 January 18 (Box 22, Folder 577-578)
        - Alice Mae "Jo" Hunt, 1991 January 19 (Box 22, Folder 579)
        - Guiva Hazelwood Barger and Jimmy Barger, 1991 January 20 (Box 22, Folder 580)
        - Jenifer Anne Stone, 1991 January 20 (Box 22, Folder 581)
        - Jenifer Anne Stone and Payton Stone, 1991 January 20 (Box 22, Folder 582)
        - Payton Stone, 1991 January 20 (Box 22, Folder 583-585)
        - Carl McSpadden, 1991 January 21 (Box 22, Folder 586)
        - Thurmon Bailey, 1991 January 22 (Box 22, Folder 587)
        - Loy Cannon, 1991 January 22 (Box 22, Folder 588)
        - Emaglah Faust Burleson, Ruth Faust Hartwick, Abigail Faust Galloway, and Eula Faust Mannon, 1991 January 27 (Box 22, Folder 589)
        - Ruth Faust Hartwick, 1991 January 27 (Box 22, Folder 590)
        - Mike Haile, Samuel Haile, Jr., and Steve Haile, 1991 Jan 31 (Box 22, Folder 591)
        - Kenzie Hannah, 1991 January 31 (Box 22, Folder 592)
        - Frank Valentine, 1991 January 31 (Box 22, Folder 593)
        - Guy Lacy and Charlotte Stair Lacy, 1991 February 2 (Box 23, Folder 594)
        - Guy Lacy and Moran Lacy, 1991 February 2 (Box 23, Folder 595)
        - Michael Provost, 1991 February 2 (Box 23, Folder 596)
        - Nancy Provost, 1991 February 2 (Box 23, Folder 597)
        - Jim Luster, 1991 February 5 (Box 23, Folder 598)
        - Murle Luster, 1991 February 5 (Box 23, Folder 599)
        - Mitchell Stark, 1991 February 5 (Box 23, Folder 600)
        - Lee Carson, 1991 February 6 (Box 23, Folder 601)
        - Matthew Johnston and Lee Carson, 1991 February 6 (Box 23, Folder 602)
        - Hal Widener, 1991 February 9 (Box 23, Folder 603)
        - Betty Utley and Hazel Cain Tate, 1991 February 11 (Box 23, Folder 604)
        - Bonnie Kay Buerkle and Christina Belcher, 1991 February 13 (Box 23, Folder 605)
        - Everett Henson, 1991 February 13 (Box 23, Folder 606)
        - Leisel McSpadden, Karen McSpadden, and Julie McSpadden, 1991 February 16 (Box 23, Folder 607)
        - Douglas Privitt, 1991 February 16 (Box 23, Folder 608)
        - Merrell Stark, 1991 February 17 (Box 23, Folder 609)
        - Howard "Rip" Collins, 1991 February 19 (Box 23, Folder 610)
        - Duane Hada, 1991 February 19 (Box 23, Folder 611)
        - Diane Bell Johnston, 1991 February 19 (Box 23, Folder 612)
        - Richard Reynolds, 1991 February 19 (Box 23, Folder 613)
        - J. A. Kirkpatrick, 1991 February 21 (Box 23, Folder 614)
        - Roland Edgar Garlinghouse, Gail Garlinghouse, and sons, 1991 March 1 (Box 23, Folder 615)
      - Pueblo Artists, Portraits
        - Views of San Ildefonso, New Mexico, 1995 May 31 (Box 24, Folder 616)
        - Views of White Mesa, San Ildefonso, New Mexico, 1995 May 31 (Box 24, Folder 617)
        - Alfred Aguilar, 1995 June 1 (Box 24, Folder 618)
        - Juan Tafoya, 1995 June 1 (Box 24, Folder 619-620)
        - Lonnie Vigil, 1995 October 16 (Box 24, Folder 621-622)
        - Bob Hazous, 1995 October 26 (Box 24, Folder 623-624)
        - Nelson Tsosie, 1995 November 8 (Box 24, Folder 625)
        - Gregory Lomayesva, 1995 November 13 (Box 24, Folder 626)
        - Estella Loretto and Fawn Eagle-Day, 1995 November 22 (Box 24, Folder 627-628)
        - Florence Aguilar Naranjo, 1995 November 30 (Box 24, Folder 629)
        - Mark Swazo-Hinds, 1995 December 4 (Box 24, Folder 630-631)
        - Bernice Moquino, 1995 December 14 (Box 24, Folder 632)
        - Corn Moquino, 1995 December 14 (Box 24, Folder 633)
        - Jody Naranjo, Dolly Naranjo Neikrug, and Jade, 1995 December 17 (Box 24, Folder 634)
        - Dolly Naranjo Neikrug, 1995 December 17 (Box 24, Folder 635)
        - Lu Ann Tafoya and Michelle Browning, 1995 December 17 (Box 24, Folder 636)
        - Lu Ann Tafoya, 1995 December 17 (Box 24, Folder 637)
        - Margarete Bagshaw-Tindel, 1996 April 12 (Box 25, Folder 638)
        - Pablita Velarde, 1996 April 12 (Box 25, Folder 639-641)
        - Charles T. Lewis, Susan Roller, Margaret Tafoya, and Toni Roller, 1996 April 24 (Box 25, Folder 642)
        - Margaret Tafoya, 1996 April 24 (Box 25, Folder 643-644)
        - Joseph Naranjo, 1996 May 2 (Box 25, Folder 645)
        - Mollie Naranjo, 1996 May 2 (Box 25, Folder 646)
        - Margarete Bagshaw-Tindel, 1996 May 15 (Box 25, Folder 647)
        - Pablita Velarde, 1996 May 15 (Box 25, Folder 648)
        - Anthony Durand, 1996 June 6 (Box 25, Folder 649-652)
        - Anthony Durand and Cora L. Durand, 1996 June 6 (Box 25, Folder 653)
        - Cora L. Durand, 1996 June 6 (Box 25, Folder 654)
        - Rose Naranjo, Dolly Naranjo Neikrug, Jody Naranjo, Jade Chavez, and Coral Chavez, 1996 June 8 (Box 25, Folder 655)
        - Phillip C. Martinez, 1996 August 7 (Box 26, Folder 656)
        - Lydia Tsosie and Carl Tsosie, 1996 August 29 (Box 26, Folder 657)
        - Augustine Lovato, 1996 September 24 (Box 26, Folder 658)
        - Ignacia Duran with daughters and granddaughters, 1996 September 25 (Box 26, Folder 659)
        - Virgie D. Nutima and Erica Leno, 1996 September 25 (Box 26, Folder 660)
        - Jean Baca, 1996 September 26 (Box 26, Folder 661)
        - Roxanne Swentzell, 1996 September 26 (Box 26, Folder 662)
        - Harry Fonseca, 1996 October 4 (Box 26, Folder 663)
        - John F. Gonzales, 1996 November 13 (Box 26, Folder 664)
        - Elizabeth Montoya, Margie Montoya, Michelle Sandoval, and Sarah Sandoval, 1996 November 13 (Box 26, Folder 665)
        - Michael Kanteena, 1996 November 19 (Box 26, Folder 666)
        - Christine McHorse, 1996 November 20 (Box 26, Folder 667)
        - Cavan Gonzales, 1996 November 22 (Box 26, Folder 668-669)
        - Robert Tenorio family, 1997 May 20 (Box 26, Folder 670)
        - Sandra M. Victorino, 1997 June 10 (Box 26, Folder 671)
      - Commissioned Portraits
        - Arthur Hecht, 1980 June 19 (Box 27, Folder 672)
        - Leslie Barclay, 1983 January 25 (Box 27, Folder 673)
        - Conrad Quintano-Mattson, 1985 August 6 (Box 27, Folder 674)
        - Emily Quintano-Mattson, 1985 August 6 (Box 27, Folder 675)
        - Tyler Quintano-Mattson, 1985 August 6 (Box 27, Folder 676)
        - Conrad Quintano-Mattson, Emily Quintano-Mattson, and Tyler Quintano-Mattson, 1985 August 6 (Box 27, Folder 677)
        - Joyce Menschel, Robert Menschel, David Menschel, and Lauren Menschel, 1986 August 29 (Box 27, Folder 678)
        - Elizabeth Kelly, 1987 August 30 (Box 27, Folder 679)
        - Jim Kelly and Elizabeth Kelly, 1987 August 30 (Box 27, Folder 680)
        - Michael Light, 1987 December 30 (Box 27, Folder 681)
        - Three generations, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 682)
        - Helen Menschel, 1988 January 16 (Box 27, Folder 683)
        - Frances Briggs and Roger Briggs, 1988 April 10 (Box 27, Folder 684-685)
        - Marshall Rose, Jill Rose, Wendy Rose, and Andrew Rose, 1989 September 2 (Box 27, Folder 686)
        - Wendy Rose, 1989 September 2 (Box 27, Folder 687)
        - Wendy Rose and Andrew Rose, 1989 September 2 (Box 27, Folder 688)
        - Alexander Warner and Blair Warner, 1989 December 27 (Box 27, Folder 689)
        - Richard Straussberg, 1999 July 10 (Box 27, Folder 690)
        - Dan Staley and Max Staley, 1999 November 21 (Box 27, Folder 691-692)
        - Harriette Tsosie and Cat Tsosie, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 693)
      - Additional Projects
        - Native American Center, Los Angeles, California
          - Ernie Peters, 1980 August 21 (Box 28, Folder 694)
          - David Bydone, 1980 August 27 (Box 28, Folder 695-696)
          - Nancy Cherley, 1980 August 27 (Box 28, Folder 697-698)
          - John Dawson, 1980 August 27 (Box 28, Folder 699)
          - Gary Lee John, 1980 August 28 (Box 28, Folder 700)
          - Karen Quintana, 1980 August 28 (Box 28, Folder 701)
          - Ben Redclay, 1980 August 28 (Box 28, Folder 702-705)
          - Russell Piper, 1980 August 28 (Box 28, Folder 706)
          - Manual Womandress, 1980 August 28 (Box 28, Folder 707)
          - Anna Kolb, 1980 September 2 (Box 28, Folder 708)
          - Anna Kolb and Kris Kolb, 1980 September 2 (Box 28, Folder 709)
          - Joe Lussier, 1980 September 2 (Box 28, Folder 710)
          - Cindy White, 1980 September 2 (Box 28, Folder 711)
          - Danielle Perkins, 1980 September 3 (Box 28, Folder 712)
        - Montaukett Indian Portraits
          - Robert D. Cooper, 1986 December 8 (Box 29, Folder 713)
          - Daniel Pharoah, 1988 January 10 (Box 29, Folder 714)
          - George M. Pharoah, Jr., 1988 January 10 (Box 29, Folder 715)
          - Olive Pharoah, 1988 January 10 (Box 29, Folder 716)
          - Robert Pharoah and Tami Pharoah, 1988 January 10 (Box 29, Folder 717)
          - Tami Pharoah, 1988 January 10 (Box 29, Folder 718)
          - Carolyn Pharoah, 1988 January 24 (Box 29, Folder 719)
          - Olive Pharoah, Peggy Butler, and Carolyn Pharoah, 1988 February 13 (Box 29, Folder 720)
          - Frederick S. Pharoah, 1988 April 12 (Box 29, Folder 721)
      - Personal Portraits
        - Darcy, 1977 April (Box 30, Folder 722)
        - Mike, a Chippewa Indian, 1977 April (Box 30, Folder 723)
        - Sarah Pato, 1977 April (Box 30, Folder 724-725)
        - Gail at Valleyfair amusement park, Shakopee, Minnesota, 1977 May (Box 30, Folder 726)
        - Mark Rayborn, 1977 May (Box 30, Folder 727)
        - William Warmack, 1977 May (Box 30, Folder 728)
        - Phillip Huston, 1977 July (Box 30, Folder 729)
        - Toby Old, 1977 August (Box 30, Folder 730)
        - Soho (South of Houston Street, Greene Street, New York, New York), 1977 August (Box 30, Folder 731-733)
        - Badou Kasse, 1977 August 5 (Box 30, Folder 734)
        - Proud Man, Broome Street, New York, New York, 1977 August 5 (Box 30, Folder 735)
        - Juan Rivera, 1977 August 16 (Box 30, Folder 736)
        - Dena Tucker, 1977 September and 1978 May 24 (Box 30, Folder 737-740)
        - Alan Gustafson, 1978 August 29 (Box 31, Folder 741)
        - Self-portrait, San Francisco, California, 1978 August 28 (Box 31, Folder 742)
        - Danielle Blackman and Juliet Blackman, 1981 January 27 (Box 31, Folder 743)
        - Samuel Locke Highleyman, III, 1981 February 8 (Box 31, Folder 744-745)
        - Gretta Keene Sabinson and Allen Sabinson, 1981 November 27 (Box 31, Folder 746)
        - Danielle Blackman, 1982 December 31 (Box 31, Folder 747)
        - Juliet Blackman, 1982 December 31 (Box 31, Folder 748)
        - Danielle Blackman and Juliet Blackman, 1982 December 31 (Box 31, Folder 749)
        - Gretta Keene Sabinson, 1982 July 7 (Box 31, Folder 750-751)
        - Petrified Forest National Park, Arizona, 1983 September 5 (Box 31, Folder 752-758)
        - Linda Pato, 1983 December 7 (Box 31, Folder 759)
        - Robert Giard, 1984 September 23 (Box 31, Folder 760)
        - Gene Thornton, 1984 December 9 (Box 31, Folder 761)
        - Colorado, 1987 August (Box 32, Folder 762-766)
        - Gunnison River, Colorado, 1987 August (Box 32, Folder 767)
        - Three Rivers Resort and Outfitting, Almont, Colorado, 1987 August 1 (Box 32, Folder 768-769)
        - Carolyn Marx, 1987 September 22 (Box 32, Folder 770-771)
        - Danielle Blackman, 1990 March 11 (Box 32, Folder 772-773)
        - Chaco Culture National Historical Park, New Mexico, 1996 May 4 (Box 32, Folder 774-780)
      - Portraits of Toba Tucker by Daytop Village Residents
        Photographs of Tucker taken by residents of Daytop Village, as well as self-portraits created in the course of the Daytop Village Portraits Project
        Photographs are arranged chronologically.
        - Self-portrait, 1978 December 5 (Box 33, Folder 781)
        - Peter Collins, 1979 February 1 (Box 33, Folder 782)
        - Luis Carrera, 1979 April 11 (Box 33, Folder 783)
        - Don Johnson, 1979 June 20 (Box 33, Folder 784)
        - Dawn Dreyfuss, 1979 July 18 (Box 33, Folder 785)
        - Socrates Gianis, 1979 September 16 (Box 33, Folder 786)
        - Karen Monaco, 1979 November 18 (Box 33, Folder 787)
        - Jesus Carrion, 1979 November 20 (Box 33, Folder 788)
        - Louis Del Gado, 1979 November 25 (Box 33, Folder 789)
        - Anthony Pensebene, 1979 December 20 (Box 33, Folder 790)
        - Carl Solano, 1980 January 30 (Box 33, Folder 791)
      - Collected photographs by other photographers
        Arranged by the surname of the photographer and then chronologically
        - Roger Haile
          - Toba Tucker, 1978 November (Box 34, Folder 792)
            Includes 2 film negatives by Haile that depict Tucker
        - Julie Jensen
          - Toba Tucker, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 793)
        - Toby Old
          - Man and Toba Tucker, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 794)
          - Bejeweled Man, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 795)
          - Body Builder, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 796)
          - Dancer, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 797)
          - Drum Majorette, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 798)
          - Man and Trailer, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 799)
          - Mime, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 800)
          - Patriotic Man, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 801)
          - Woman at White Castle, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 802)
          - Wrestler, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 803)
        - George Steeves
          - Rear of 5450 Victoria Road, Halifax, 1980 May 11 (Box 34, Folder 804)
          - Ivy Wall, 5680 Inglis Street, Halifax, 1980 July 18 (Box 34, Folder 805)
          - Nude and Breakfast Table, 1981 December 26 (Box 34, Folder 806)
          - Boer War Monument, Granville and George Streets, Halifax, 1982 June 6 (Box 34, Folder 807)
          - Woman, 1983 December, 1984 August 30 (Box 34, Folder 808-809)
        - Joel Sternfeld
          - Milford, Connecticut, 1978 July (Box 34, Folder 810)
          - Beach, cliffs, and hang gliders, undated (Box 34, Folder 811)
        - Maxine Walker
          - Jason Fearon, Dancer, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 812)
    - 16 inches by 20 inches
      - Daytop Village Portraits
        - Larry Jackson and Ernesto Carrera, 1978 February 17 (Box 35, Folder 813)
        - Chris Frassa, 1978 October 24 (Box 35, Folder 814)
        - Mike Davis, 1978 October 26 (Box 35, Folder 815)
        - Peter Morgan, 1978 November 1 (Box 35, Folder 816)
        - Magda Velez, 1978 November 14 (Box 35, Folder 817)
        - Beatrice Monroe, 1978 December 5 (Box 35, Folder 818)
        - Luis Carrera, 1979 April 13 (Box 35, Folder 819)
        - Kelsey Sutton, 1979 April 13 (Box 35, Folder 820)
        - Frank Moya, 1979 April 20 (Box 35, Folder 821)
        - John Hepburn, 1979 May 8 (Box 35, Folder 822)
        - Denis Kelly, 1979 May 17 (Box 35, Folder 823)
        - Ida De Jesus, 1979 June 6 (Box 35, Folder 824)
        - Phil Hefft, 1979 June 26 (Box 35, Folder 825)
        - Joe Adams, 1979 June 26 (Box 35, Folder 826)
        - Henry Alvarez, 1979 June 27 (Box 35, Folder 827)
        - Dennis Knoop, 1979 July 5 (Box 36, Folder 828)
        - Phil Carroll, 1979 June 18 (Box 36, Folder 829)
        - Phil Maurer, 1979 July 18 (Box 36, Folder 830)
        - Mark Hoban, 1979 July 19 (Box 36, Folder 831)
        - Fred Botway, 1979 July 19 (Box 36, Folder 832)
        - Carl Solano, 1979 July 29 (Box 36, Folder 833)
        - Lorraine Cowan, 1979 August 21 (Box 36, Folder 834)
        - Brad Packer, 1979 September 18 (Box 36, Folder 835-836)
        - Edwin Marcucci, 1979 October 24 (Box 36, Folder 837)
        - Reid Barnett, 1979 October 24 (Box 37, Folder 838)
        - Carolyn Burke, 1979 November 20 (Box 37, Folder 839)
        - Jesus Carrion, 1979 November 20 (Box 37, Folder 840-842)
        - Jesus Correa, 1979 December 20 (Box 37, Folder 843)
        - Reid Barnett, 1980 January 18 (Box 37, Folder 844)
        - Carl Solano, 1980 January 18 (Box 37, Folder 845)
        - Trinessa Wilson, 1980 February 27 (Box 37, Folder 846)
        - Beatrice Monroe, 1980 April 8 (Box 37, Folder 847)
        - Luis Carrera, 1980 April 8 (Box 37, Folder 848-849)
      - Navajo Portraits
        - Ned Washee, 1981 June 8 (Box 38, Folder 850)
        - Kalutah, 1981 June 9 (Box 38, Folder 851)
        - Selina James, 1981 June 12 (Box 38, Folder 852)
        - Louise Bahe, 1981 June 12 (Box 38, Folder 853)
        - Bernice Begay and Bah Chee, 1981 June 16 (Box 38, Folder 854)
        - Marlene Bahe, 1981 June 16 (Box 38, Folder 855)
        - Ruby Gishal and Betty Bedoni, 1981 June 17 (Box 38, Folder 856)
        - Elvira Morgan and Martha Morgan, 1981 June 18 (Box 38, Folder 857)
        - Merlinda Lewis and Patrick Lewis, 1981 June 18 (Box 38, Folder 858)
        - William Begay, Sr., 1981 June 22 (Box 38, Folder 859)
        - Sally Chee, 1981 June 22 (Box 38, Folder 860)
        - Clark Tsosie, 1981 June 22 (Box 38, Folder 861)
        - Hasteen Bob, 1981 June 22 (Box 38, Folder 862)
      - Navajo Portraits - Color
        - Kalutah, 1981 June 9 (Box 39, Folder 863)
        - Ned Washee, 1981 June 9 (Box 39, Folder 864)
        - Bernice Begay, 1981 June 11 (Box 39, Folder 865)
        - Mary Yazzi, 1981 June 11 (Box 39, Folder 866)
        - Zonnie Bahe, 1981 June 12 (Box 39, Folder 867)
        - Selina James, 1981 June 12 (Box 39, Folder 868)
        - Bennie H. James and Gilbert James, 1981 June 12 (Box 39, Folder 869)
        - Louise Bahe, 1981 June 12 (Box 39, Folder 870)
        - Tony K. John, 1981 June 12 (Box 39, Folder 871)
        - Bernice Begay and Bah Chee, 1981 June 16 (Box 39, Folder 872)
        - Mary Pete Nelson, 1981 June 16 (Box 39, Folder 873-874)
        - Elle Benally, 1981 June 16 (Box 39, Folder 875)
        - Moonrise at Jeddito, Arizona, 1981 June 16 (Box 39, Folder 876)
        - Hogan at Jeddito, Arizona, 1981 June 16 (Box 39, Folder 877)
        - Ruby Gishal and Betty Bedoni, 1981 June 17 (Box 39, Folder 878)
        - Ray G. Chee, 1981 June 17 (Box 39, Folder 879)
        - Elvira Morgan and Martha Morgan, 1981 June 18 (Box 40, Folder 880)
        - Kenneth Jensen, 1981 June 18 (Box 40, Folder 881)
        - Joseph W. Nelson, 1981 June 18 (Box 40, Folder 882-883)
        - Thelma Yellowhair, 1981 June 18 (Box 40, Folder 884)
        - John B. Nez, 1981 June 18 (Box 40, Folder 885)
        - Merlinda Lewis and Patrick Lewis, 1981 June 18 (Box 40, Folder 886)
        - Sally Elizabeth Bahe and Emma Bahe, 1981 June 22 (Box 40, Folder 887)
        - William Begay, Sr., 1981 June 22 (Box 40, Folder 888)
        - Hasteen Bob, 1981 June 22 (Box 40, Folder 889)
        - Clark Tsosie, 1981 June 22 (Box 40, Folder 890)
        - Sally Chee and Melissa Begay, 1981 June 22 (Box 40, Folder 891)
        - Landscape Teesto, Arizona, 1981 June 23 (Box 40, Folder 892-894)
        - Anita Begay, 1981 December 3 (Box 40, Folder 895)
        - Henry James, 1981 December 3 (Box 40, Folder 896)
        - Stella Begay, 1981 December 3 (Box 40, Folder 897)
        - Chester Yellowhair, 1981 December 3 (Box 40, Folder 898)
        - Pauline Yellowhair, 1981 December 3 (Box 40, Folder 899)
        - Juanita Clark, 1981 December 3 (Box 40, Folder 900)
      - Shinnecock Indians of Eastern Long Island Portraits
        - Phillip Brown, Jr., 1984 September 25 (Box 41, Folder 901)
        - Garland Gill, 1984 October 5 (Box 41, Folder 902)
        - Edward Gumbs, 1984 October 7 (Box 41, Folder 903-904)
        - Arnay Terry and Terrell Terry, 1984 October 7 (Box 41, Folder 905)
        - Terrell Terry, 1984 October 7 (Box 41, Folder 906)
        - Arlene Butler, 1984 October 12 (Box 41, Folder 907)
        - Paulina Kirby, 1984 October 18 (Box 41, Folder 908)
        - Naike Bess, 1984 December 15 (Box 41, Folder 909)
        - Wayne Duncan, 1984 December 23 (Box 41, Folder 910)
        - Eloise Eleazer, 1984 December 30 (Box 41, Folder 911)
        - Eloise Eleazer and Jolanda Eleazer, 1984 December 30 (Box 41, Folder 912)
        - Constance Cuffee Valdez, 1985 March 2 (Box 41, Folder 913)